Contact

Jl. Raya Ciomas Gg. Saleh Rt.003 Rw.005 Kelurahan Padasuka, Kecamatan Ciomas, Kabupaten Bogor, Jawa Barat - Indonesia +6282114578976 (Mobile) adam.pm77@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/adampm (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Filament Visual Web Developer Next.js

Languages

Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)
Sundanese (Limited Working)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Belajar RESTful API untuk Pemula HRD Training Belajar HTTP untuk Pemula

Adam Prasetya Malik

Web Development

West Java, Indonesia

Summary

I have multimedia background.

My experiences are related with

- Trainer / Teacher / Instructor
- Game Operational
- Web Development

Currently work as Web Developer at PT Sistegra Emran Sentosa Feel free if there any question about myself by send me email at adam.pm77@gmail.com or contact me at +62-821-145-789-76

Experience

Sistegra Emran Sentosa, PT Web Developer November 2024 - Present (3 months) Cibinong, West Java, Indonesia

Freelance

Freelance Web Developer January 2018 - Present (7 years 1 month) Bogor

The work that has been made:

- Expeditions Application for "5 Waktu Logistic"
- Point of Sales (POS) Application for "Pekgo Apparel"
- Cashier application for "Toko Ananda Dramaga"
- Inventory & Sales Application for "PT. Fujibolt Indonesia"
- Company Profile for "CV. Wanammi"
- Crypto Asset Application for "Cryptoperty"
- Online shop for "Pekgo Group"
- Apjiigolf.id for Persatuan Golf APJII (PGA)

Jala Lintas Media Web Developer

October 2022 - October 2024 (2 years 1 month)

Cibinong, West Java, Indonesia

Website I create:

- bnetfit.id
- jlm.net.id
- netvolve.id
- business.bnetfit.id
- air.bnetfit.id
- jak-inet.com

KSPPS Baytul Ikhtiar (BAIK)

Information Technology Supporter March 2019 - October 2020 (1 year 8 months) Bogor

- LAN & WAN technician
- Web Application Development
- Computer or Laptop repair
- Fingerprint installation and support

CV. Rimsmedia

Web Programmer

July 2017 - December 2017 (6 months)

Bogor

Handle all request for create an application web based

PT. Kreon - Gemscool

Game Operations

July 2013 - June 2017 (4 years)

Gedung Gandaria 8 Unit B-C Lt.20 Jl. Sultan Iskandar Muda, Kebayoran Lama 12240

Handle User Complain

Quality Assurance Game

Social Media Management

Event Planer

Intermis, Multi Media Arto Sentosa Data Entry Operator June 2012 - March 2013 (10 months)

Indonesia

Data Entry and Data Processor

RoboKidz Instructor Robotic August 2011 - June 2012 (11 months) Bogor

Teaching the Concept of Robotics with Lego Education

SMK Informatika Bina Generasi Honorary Teacher Multimedia June 2010 - June 2011 (1 year 1 month) Bogor

Basic teaching animation concept with Adobe Flash and basic design with Adobe Photoshop

CV. Cahaya Berlian Sejati (CBS) IT Support January 2010 - June 2010 (6 months) Bogor

- Assistant Phographer & Web Developer
- Manager Division Bogor Photography Course (BPC)

PT. Mitrasoft Global IT Support 2009 - 2010 (1 year) Bojong Gede

IT Support Islamic Banking Application

Takaful Mikro Indonesia (TAKMIN) IT Support 2009 - 2009 (less than a year) Bogor

Yayasan Peramu IT Support 2008 - 2009 (1 year) Bogor

Education

SMK Informatika Bina Generasi MM, Multimedia · (2006 - 2008)